icolancer.com 2018-01-10

# Privacy Policy | Icolancer

Your privacy and trust are significant to us and this Privacy Statement (“Statement”) provides pertinent information about how Icolancer and its affiliated services (hereby can be called as “Icolancer,” “we,” “us,” or Collectively as “Icolancer sites”) handle personal information. This Statement applies to any Icolancer website, application, product, software, or service that links to it (collectively, our “Services”). Occasionally, a Service will link to a different Privacy Statement that will outline the particular privacy practices of that Service.

Please read this Statement carefully and if you have any questions about our privacy practices or your personal information choices, you can contact us at hello@Icolancer. It is important that you regularly check for updates to this Statement.

**Personal Information**

Icolancer is committed to the responsible handling and protection of personal information.

Personal information means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person; an identifiable person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural, or social identity of that person.

We collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store personal information when needed to provide our Services and for our operational and business purposes as described in this Statement. We want to be clear about our privacy practices so that you can make informed choices about the use of your information, and we encourage you to contact us at any time with questions or concerns.

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

Some of our Web pages utilize “cookies” and other tracking technologies. A “cookie” is a text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Web site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to block the cookies, you will need to special permissions to gain access to certain parts of the Web site.

Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allow us to improve our Web site and your Web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain personal information for trends and statistics.

**Using your Information**

Our primary goal in collecting user information is to enhance your experience on our website.

We use cookies to:

**To Target Content and Advertising**

To develop and provide content and advertising to you that is targeted to your interests, we use the analytics collected by the systems described above to determine which areas of our website you prefer based upon the frequency of your visits and engagement with those areas. We may make reasonable assumptions based on your browser provided data to target relevant content and advertising to you on our site and elsewhere where we may be acting as a 3rd party. We may also make reasonable geographic and demographic assumptions based on your presented IP address to target relevant content and advertising.

**To Provide Interactive Communications From Icolancer**

To enhance your experience we may provide you with interactive communications, such as notifications of activity by topic or contributor to the e-mail address that you provide to us. Such interactive communications are provided only to those users who have expressly provided us with their permission to receive them as part of their user profile.

From time to time we may provide e-mails highlighting new features, promotions or contests on the website to those users who have expressly provided us with their permission to send such communications as part of their user profile.

**To Provide Communications From Third Parties**

We respect the privacy of our users and shall not disclose or distribute our user list to any third party, nor shall we permit anyone else to do so. However, we do make available for rental our list of those registrants who have expressly provided us with their permission to receive third party offers as part of their user profile. In those cases, your email address will not be transferred to the third party.

**Consent to Your Information**

By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Terms of Use and to the Icolancer processing of personal information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where we collect personal information on the Web. Should there be changes to the Terms of Use, please ensure that you frequently visit these changes.

**Confidentiality and Security**

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with the laws prevalent in India to protect personal information about you. We seek to ensure compliance with the requirements of the Information Technology Act, 2000 and rules made there under to ensure the protection and preservation of your privacy.
